http://www.discovertheworld.com/privacy

Get in touch
Headquarters:
+1 480-707-5566
14350 N 87th St, Suite 320,
Scottsdale, Arizona 85260
USA
London Regional Center:
+44 0203 598 8030
Studio 403, VOX Studios
1 – 45 Durham Street,
London SE11 5JH
United Kingdom
Email: info@discovertheworld.com
Use the form below to send us a message.
Name: *required field
Surname: *required field
Email: *required field
Mobile number:
Landline number:
Address:
Address line 2:
Your message: *required field
the captcha failed to validate.
Please wait while we process your request...
Latin America
ArgentinaBoliviaBrazilChileColombiaCosta RicaEcuadorEl SalvadorGuatemalaPanamaParaguayPeruUruguay
Europe
AustriaBelgiumCzech RepublicDenmarkFinlandFranceGermanyGreeceHungaryIrelandItalyLuxembourgMaltaNetherlandsNorwayPolandPortugalRussiaSlovakiaSpainSwedenSwitzerlandTurkeyUkraineUnited KingdomWest Balkans
M.East & Africa
Eastern AfricaIsraelMiddle EastSouth Africa
Asia
ChinaHong Kong SARIndiaIndonesiaJapanMalaysiaPhilippinesSingaporeSouth KoreaSri LankaTaiwan ROCThailandVietnam
South Pacific
AustraliaNew Zealand
Our Clients
Our world
Contact Us
MENU
About us
Our Services
Privacy Policy
Last updated on May 25, 2018.
Discover Momentum L.L.C. (Discover the World and its affiliates, collectively “Discover the World” or “We”) is a travel related services company with global operations in many countries. We provide travel sales, marketing services, business process outsourcing, and risk management for our global customers (our “Services”).
We strongly believe in transparency and respecting your online privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it, in the context of our services and when you visit our websites (“Sites”).
Why We Collect Personal Information
Personal information enables us to identify you when providing our Services. We collect personal information from our Sites’ visitors, for marketing purposes and to improve our Services, and our customers for the provision of our Services, which may include:
Travel booking
Travel assistance
Online account management
Account billing
Communication
Surveys
Fraud prevention and detection
Internal research and product development
The personal information we collect is required to perform our contracts Services. Without it, we would not be able to offer our Services and fulfill your requests.
We also collect personal information for the purposes of direct-marketing.
The Personal Information We Collect
The personal information that we collect for the above purposes may include: name, phone number, email and physical address, gender, age, date of birth, form of payment and card numbers, travel preferences where expressed (seat, meal, smoking, special services, etc.), passport and visa details, Passenger Name Record (PNR), and emergency contact information.
We also collect personal information from visitors to our websites via “Contact Us”, “Registration”, “Newsletter Subscription” online forms, whose fields contain name, surname, email, mobile and landline numbers, physical address, and any other personal information you choose to provide.
How We Collect Your Personal Information
We typically collect your personal information through providing our services either through feeds from corporate clients or by you or the traveler. We may also receive personal information from online booking tools or the reservations systems of other organizations.
For group travel, we process travelers lists received from clients or indirectly through online management providers that may be selected by the client.
Cookies
We may use cookies to identify you and track your use of the Sites to improve your user experience, tailor Site interactions, deliver content specific to your interests, provide support, and administer and improve the Site. Cookies are small files placed on your computer by the Site for identification purposes. Cookies identify you to the Site and are used to load your preferences and track the pages you visit.
Web browsers may be configured to automatically accept cookies, and most will allow you to modify the way cookies are handled. You may be able to configure your web browser to warn you when it receives a cookie in order to be given a choice to accept or reject the cookie, or you may be able to configure your browser to automatically refuse cookies. See the "Help" menu of your browser or its company’s website to learn how to change cookie preferences in your browser.
Our sites do not respond to browser "Do Not Track" (“DNT”) requests.
Use of Your Personal Information
We use your personal information to provide our Services as described above. In some cases, this requires us to share your personal information with governments and third parties, including some that may be physically located in or store their information in other countries.
Retention of Personal Information
We retain your personal information only as long as needed to provide our services, meet our contractual agreements, adhere to applicable laws, legal obligations disputes, claims or other litigation, and respond to inquiries related to past travel and activities to meet our policies and customer commitments.
Sharing of Personal Information
To provide our Services, support your needs, and in line with travel industry practices, We may need to share your personal information with various third-parties, including:
Travel industry service providers (cruise lines, airlines, hotels, car rental companies, etc.)
Central reservation systems
Card payment companies or banks
Government bodies, from time to time, to respond to applicable laws or specific requests
Your travel or other benefits of our Services may not be possible without our sharing of your personal information.
We may use authorized third-parties to process your personal information for certain administrative functions. These Processors may have access to your personal information but only for, on behalf of, and under our instructions, and are required to adhere to our policies, standards, and processes, as well as any applicable laws, as part of our agreement.
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to requesting government authorities, if required to do so by law, or in good faith that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with applicable laws.
Transfer of Personal Information
Given the international nature of Services, international personal information transfers are made throughout the regular course of business. When your personal information is transferred to, or centrally stored in, a country that does not offer a similar level of protection as the European Economic Area (“EEA”), We will take reasonable precautions to ensure an adequate level of protection of the transferred information. This may include, but is not limited to, inter-company information transfer agreements based on the European Standard Contractual Clauses that may be part of a Data Processing Agreement (“DPA”).
Protecting Your Personal Information
We have implemented and maintain appropriate administrative, physical, and technical safeguards to ensure the confidentiality, integrity, availability of your personal information. These measures are monitored to prevent the accidental or unlawful alteration, destruction, disclosure, or processing of your personal information.
Direct Marketing Communications
Visitors to our Sites are welcome to browse, and you can always elect not to provide us your personal information. However, you may be unable to access certain services that involve our interaction with you.
If you have received a communication from us regarding our products or services, it is either because you have requested such communication or because we believe the communication is of interest to you or your company, based on earlier activity. In some cases, we may have collected your contact details from a third-party with whom you agreed onward sharing. We rely on this legitimate interest to keep you informed of our products and services. However, if you no longer wish to receive further marketing communications, please click on the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of any marketing communication or email privacy@discovertheworld.com and we will cease all communications for that purpose.
We will retain your personal information for marketing purposes only so long as you wish to receive our marketing communications. Please request to ‘unsubscribe’ from marketing communications if you no longer wish us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
Your Rights
You may be entitled to several rights over your personal information and how it is used. These may include the rights of access, rectification, deletion, or objection to the processing of your personal information on legitimate grounds.
If you wish to exercise any of these rights, or have questions on our privacy practices, please email privacy@discovertheworld.com We will review and respond to your request within 30 days. However, if you are not satisfied with our response, and depending on the country in which you reside, you may also have a right to file a complaint with a supervisory authority. Please contact our Privacy Administrator regarding questions of this right or any other concerns.
Contact
To contact us with questions or issues about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at Privacy@DiscovertheWorld.com.
The use, processing or transfer of your personal information may be regulated by applicable information protection and privacy regulations. Accordingly, this policy may be updated as required. The current version will always be posted here, but we advise reviewing our Privacy Policy from time to time. The continued use of our Site and Services is acknowledgement of the Privacy Policy posted at that time.
Privacy Policy
©2020 Discover the World.
v3.0
